<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About DAYMUNC on DAYMUNC</title>
    <link>https://daymunc.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About DAYMUNC on DAYMUNC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 19:48:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daymunc.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/awards/</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Award Guidelines DAYMUNC offers awards to delegates that demonstrate exemplary diplomacy, negotiation and speaking skills, technical research capabilities, and facilitate committee. An award is also presented for Outstanding Position Paper, which is submitted prior to the conference.
Award Structure Each committee will present 1 outstanding delegate award, 1 distinguished delegate award, and 3 honorable mentions at closing ceremony. This is determined by the individual ratings and deliberations between the committee Director, Chair, and Rapporteur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SC</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/committees/sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/committees/sc/</guid>
      <description>Security Council Committee Topics:
I. The Situation in Hong Kong
II. Protecting Women from Violent Extremism and Violent Non-State Actors
Committee Documents:
Background Guide will be available Sunday, November 17, 2019.
Staff: Director: Christian Cooper
Chair: Caleb Jackson
Rapporteur: Caroline Hoffman
If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GA3</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/committees/csw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/committees/csw/</guid>
      <description>GA3 Committee Topics:
I. Combatting Xenophobia and Systemic Abuse of Muslims and Other Religious Minorities
II. Promoting Food Security and Public Health in Yemen
Committee Documents:
Background Guide is available here (/uploads/2019/11/19/GA3 BBG DAYMUNC XXVII Final .docx &amp;ldquo;GA3 BBG DAYMUNC XXVII Final .docx&amp;rdquo;).
Staff: Director: Sam Pugh
Chair: Nickii Cottrell
Rapporteur: Ivan Mallett
If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/staff.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 20:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/staff.html</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Staff Information Message from the Secretary General Hello! My name is Autumn Kern and I am the Secretary General for DAYMUNC 2020. I completed my undergraduate degree in Political Science and International Studies from Wright State University. I am currently a Master of Art in International and Comparative Politics student at the Wright State Graduate School, where I am studying the involvement of women in militant Islamic groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procedures</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:55:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/procedures/</guid>
      <description>Rules Of Procedure DAYMUNC Rules of Parliamentary Procedure and Bylaws A complete, indexed description of all DAYMUNC rules of parliamentary procedure and conference bylaws.
DAYMUNC Rules (Short Form) DAYMUNC points and motions listed in order of precedence. Useful as a reference in committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/hotel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/hotel/</guid>
      <description>HOTEL RESERVATIONS Once again this year we have reserved rooms at the Marriott University of Dayton near the University of Dayton campus. The room rate per night is $114.00. Although breakfast is not included there is a full scale restaurant and snack area to purchase reasonably priced meals, snacks, and beverages. Also, breakfast items will be provided in the morning during the conference. The Marriott University of Dayton is located on 1414 South Patterson Boulevard, Dayton, Ohio 45409.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/gallery/</guid>
      <description>Gallery The gallery is actively being developed, but is in need of pictures! If you or your team have any current or past pictures they would like hosted on this page, please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to send them over to secgen.daymunc@gmail.com
wHXWRmkGKo7RwAGy64am84JmzpoNhRwVN9</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Schedule</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 20:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Conference Schedule Conference will be held:
February 7th-8th, 2020
The schedule for DAYMUNC XXVII will be uploaded at a later date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Directions</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/directions/</guid>
      <description>Getting to DAYMUNC The 2020 Dayton Model United Nations Conference (DAYMUNC XXVII) will be held at:
 David H. Ponitz Center, Sinclair Community College, Building 12 (1st and 2nd floors) 444 West Third Street, Dayton, OH 45402-1460 Feb. 7-8, 2020
 Conveniently located in downtown Dayton, Sinclair Center can be reached quickly and easily from nearby hotels and highways.
 Take the Third Street exit 53A off of I-75 (northbound or southbound) Turn right on Perry Street Turn right on Fourth Street, then right again into the underground parking garage beneath Sinclair Center  Delegates may park in the Sinclair student garage ($5 per day) or use metered parking (free on weekends) around the College campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Position Papers</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/positionpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 20:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/positionpapers/</guid>
      <description>Position Paper Submission Procedure and Deadline  The DAYMUNC papers must be submitted in both WORD and PDF by the date assigned. The deadline for position papers is Friday, January 24, 2020 by 11:59 pm. Your submission email must contain the following: Subject Line in the form of: \[Committee\] Position Paper for \[Country\] - \[School\]. Body of email must contain Committee Name, Country Name, School, and Delegate&amp;#39;s name. The position paper file, attached as either a Microsoft Word (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resolution Guide</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/resolutions/</guid>
      <description> Resolution Guide Resolutions are the primary type of document procured by policy making bodies such as the General Assembly that puts forth sentiments and solutions to issues. Each committee at DAYMUNC will involve resolution writing. For guidance related to how to write resolutions properly, delegates may consult some of the following resources:
 Resolution Template (document)
 DAYMUNC Resolution Buzzwords
 DAYMUNC Resolution Writing Guide
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBC</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/committees/unea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 19:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/committees/unea/</guid>
      <description>Peace-Building Commission Committee Topics:
I. Increasing Women&amp;rsquo;s Participation in Integrated Strategies for Post-Conflict Peace-Building and Recovery
II. The Situation in Syria
Background Guide will be available Sunday, November 17, 2019.
Staff: Director: Angie Lloyd
Chair: Rahima Hamadi
Rapporteur: Hannah Hays
If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attend Daymunc</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/attend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 17:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/attend/</guid>
      <description>Attendance Information If you are interested in attending DAYMUNC {{&amp;lt; 2020&amp;gt;}}, email the Secretary General at secgen.daymunc@gmail.com.
DAYMUNC registration fee: PAYMENT OF DAYMUNC DELEGATE FEES:
The payment fee per delegate is $45. However, if this is your first time attending the conference, we are offering a discount rate of $35 per delegate. The option for payment of DAYMUNC Delegate fees is the same as last year. Below are the following instructions by Sinclair Community College’s (SCC) Office of the Bursar on how payments are to be made:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 15:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Information Mailing Address:  ATTN: Kathy &amp;amp; Jenny Sooy 444 West Third Street Dayton, OH 45402-1460
 DAYMUNC Contact Information Secretary General:
Autumn Kern
937-951-5443
secgen.daymunc@gmail.com
Deputy Secretary General
Crystal Burns Wicklund:
secgen.daymunc@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Country Assignments</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/country/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/country/</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Country Assignments We are accepting Country Assignments starting November 13th to November 19th (early preference submission). Country Assignments can absolutely change after the early preference submission deadline.
Country Assignment Rules:  If you are attending NMUN, and we have your team’s country assignment, your delegation will have special preference for that country. Meaning your delegates are guaranteed that country for committees. (For example, if your delegation is representing the United Kingdom at NMUN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply to Staff at DAYMUNC</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.org/apply-to-staff-at-daymunc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.org/apply-to-staff-at-daymunc/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in staffing at DAYMUNC 2020!
We welcome current students, MUN Alumni, and individuals interested in the program to be involved with this conference.
Please fill out the application here.
*Applications for committee directors will be closed on September 22nd, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>