<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About DAYMUNC on DAYMUNC</title>
    <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About DAYMUNC on DAYMUNC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 15:48:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SC</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/sc/</guid>
      <description>Security Council Committee Topics:
I. Proliferation of Small Arms and Light Weapons (SALW) and its Role in Conflict in the Middle East
II. Securing Critical Infrastructure to Enhance Cybersecurity Capabilities
Committee Documents:
Background Guide for DAYMUNC is available here
Staff: If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSW</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/csw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 13:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/csw/</guid>
      <description>CSW Committee Topics:
I. The Empowerment of Rural Women in the HIV/AIDS Epidemic
II. Addressing Access to Healthcare for Refugee and Migrant Women and Girls
Committee Documents:
Background Guide for DAYMUNC is available here
Staff: If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/staff.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:58:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/staff.html</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Staff Information Message from the Secretary General Hello, my name is Nickii Webb and I am the Secretary General for the 25th Annual Dayton Model UN Conference in Feb. 2018. I am currently a Masters of Art in International and Comparative Politics student at Wright State University, studying rehabilitation programs for children affected by armed conflict and their role in post-conflict state stability. This will be my fourth year of Model UN experience, but my first year staffing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procedures</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:55:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/procedures/</guid>
      <description>Rules Of Procedure DAYMUNC Rules of Parliamentary Procedure and Bylaws A complete, indexed description of all DAYMUNC rules of parliamentary procedure and conference bylaws.
DAYMUNC Rules (Short Form) DAYMUNC points and motions listed in order of precedence. Useful as a reference in committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/hotel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:52:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/hotel/</guid>
      <description>HOTEL RESERVATIONS Once again this year we have reserved rooms at the Marriott University of Dayton near the University of Dayton campus. The room rate per night is $101.00. Although breakfast is not included there is a full scale restaurant and snack area to purchase reasonably priced meals, snacks, and beverages. Also, breakfast items will be provided in the morning during the conference. The Marriott University of Dayton is located on 1414 South Patterson Boulevard, Dayton, Ohio 45409.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:50:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/gallery/</guid>
      <description>Gallery The gallery is actively being developed, but is really in need of pictures! If you or your team has any current or past pictures they would like hosted on this page, please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to send them over to matt.piekenbrock@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Schedule</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Conference Schedule Conference will be held: Feb. 2-3, 2018
The schedule for DAYMUNC 2018 can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Directions</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/directions/</guid>
      <description>Getting to DAYMUNC The 2018 Dayton Model United Nations Conference (DAYMUNC XXV) will be held at:
 David H. Ponitz Center, Sinclair Community College, Building 12 (1st and 2nd floors) 444 West Third Street, Dayton, OH 45402-1460 Feb. 2-3, 2018
 Conveniently located in downtown Dayton, Sinclair Center can be reached quickly and easily from nearby hotels and highways.
 Take the Third Street exit 53A off of I-75 (northbound or southbound) Turn right on Perry Street Turn right on Fourth Street, then right again into the underground parking garage beneath Sinclair Center  Delegates may park in the Sinclair student garage ($5 per day) or use metered parking (free on weekends) around the College campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Position Papers</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/positionpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/positionpapers/</guid>
      <description>Position Paper Submission Procedure and Deadline  The DAYMUNC papers must be submitted in WORD Document, but not in a PDF file by the date assigned. The deadline for position papers is Jan. 27, 2018 by MIDNIGHT. Your submission email must contain the following: Subject Line in the form of: [Committee] Position Paper for [Country] - [School]. Body of email must contain Committee Name, Country Name, School, and Delegate&amp;#39;s name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resolution Guide</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/resolutions/</guid>
      <description> Resolution Guide Resolutions are the primary type of document procured by policy making bodies such as the General Assembly that puts forth sentiments and solutions to issues. Each committee at DAYMUNC will involve resolution writing. For guidance related to how to write resolutions properly, delegates may consult some of the following resources:
 Resolution Template (document)
 DAYMUNC Resolution Buzzwords
 DAYMUNC Resolution Writing Guide
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIMSEC</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/simsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 15:48:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/simsec/</guid>
      <description>SIMSEC Committee Topics:
Committee Documents:
Background Guide for DAYMUNC is available here
Staff: If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNEA</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/unea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 15:48:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/committees/unea/</guid>
      <description>UNEA Committee Topics:
I. Restoring the Sustainability of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Oceans, Seas, and Freshwater Ecosystems
II. Protection of the Environment in Areas Susceptible to Displacing Persons
Committee Documents: Background Guide for DAYMUNC is available here
Staff: If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attend Daymunc</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/attend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 13:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/attend/</guid>
      <description>Attendance Information If you are interested in attending DAYMUNC XXV, email the Secretary General at secgen.daymunc@gmail.com.
DAYMUNC registration fee: PAYMENT OF DAYMUNC DELEGATE FEES:
The payment fee per delegate is $45. We were able to keep the fee at the same rate this year. The option for payment of DAYMUNC Delegate fees is the same as last year. Below are the following instructions by Sinclair Community College’s (SCC) Office of the Bursar on how payments are to be made:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/awards/</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Award Guidelines DAYMUNC offers awards to delegates that demonstrate exemplary diplomacy, negotiation and speaking skills, technical research capabilities, and facilitate committee. These awards are for individual delegates only; team awards are not given. An award is also presented for Outstanding Position Paper, which is submitted prior to the conference.
Award Structure Each committee will present 1 outstanding delegate award, 1 distinguished delegate award, and 3 honorable mentions at closing ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Information Mailing Address:  ATTN: Kathy &amp;amp; Jenny Sooy 444 West Third Street Dayton, OH 45402-1460
 DAYMUNC Contact Information Secretary General: secgen.daymunc@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Country Assignments</title>
      <link>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/country/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daymunc.github.io/daymunc_website/country/</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Country Assignments We are accepting Country Assignments starting November 13th to November 19th (early preference submission). Country Assignments can absolutely change after the early preference submission deadline.
Country Assignment Rules:  If you are attending NMUN, and we have your team’s country assignment, your delegation will have special preference for that country. Meaning your delegates are guaranteed that country for committees. (For example, if your delegation is representing the United Kingdom at NMUN.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>