<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About DAYMUNC on DAYMUNC</title>
    <link>http://daymunc.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About DAYMUNC on DAYMUNC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 15:48:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://daymunc.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Directions</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/directions/</guid>
      <description>Getting to DAYMUNC The 2018 Dayton Model United Nations Conference (DAYMUNC XXIII) will be held at:
 David H. Ponitz Center, Sinclair Community College, Building 12 (1st and 2nd floors) 444 West Third Street, Dayton, OH 45402-1460 Jan. 5, 2018
 Conveniently located in downtown Dayton, Sinclair Center can be reached quickly and easily from nearby hotels and highways.
 Take the Third Street exit 53A off of I-75 (northbound or southbound) Turn right on Perry Street Turn right on Fourth Street, then right again into the underground parking garage beneath Sinclair Center  Delegates may park in the Sinclair student garage ($5 per day) or use metered parking (free on weekends) around the College campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Position Papers</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/positionpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 16:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/positionpapers/</guid>
      <description>Position Paper Submission Procedure and Deadline {{&amp;lt; jumbo title=&amp;ldquo;Position Paper Submission Procedure and Deadline&amp;rdquo; content=&amp;ldquo;The DAYMUNC papers must be submitted in WORD Document, but not in a PDF file by the date assigned. The deadline for position papers is January 27, 2016 by MIDNIGHT. Your submission email must contain the following: Subject Line in the form of: [Committee] Position Paper for [Country] - [School] Body of email must contain Committee Name, Country Name, School, and Delegate&amp;rsquo;s name The position paper file, attached as either a Microsoft Word (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIMSEC</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/committees/simsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 15:48:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/committees/simsec/</guid>
      <description>UNESCO Committee Topics:
Committee Documents: Background Guide for DAYMUNC is available here
Staff: If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.
strong Example Position Paper:&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNESCO</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/committees/unesco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 15:48:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/committees/unesco/</guid>
      <description>UNESCO Committee Topics:
Committee Documents: Background Guide for DAYMUNC is available here
Staff: If you are interested in applying for a staff position for DAYMUNC, please contact the Secretary General.
strong Example Position Paper:&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attend Daymunc</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/attend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 13:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/attend/</guid>
      <description>Attendance Information If you are interested in attending DAYMUNC XXIII, email the Secretary General at
DAYMUNC registration fee: Below are the following instructions by Sinclair Community College’s (SCC) Office of the Bursar on how payments are to be made:
 Sinclair requires payment of deposits or full delegate payments directly to the College Bursar’s office and John Coyle assists us with this process. If you have any questions about payment of DAYMUNC Delegate fees, you may contact Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/awards/</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Award Guidelines DAYMUNC offers awards to delegates that demonstrate exemplary diplomacy, negotiation and speaking skills, technical research capabilities, and facilitate committee. These awards are for individual delegates only; team awards are not given. An award is also presented for Outstanding Position Paper, which is submitted prior to the conference.
Award Structure Each committee will present 1 outstanding delegate award, 1 distinguished delegate award, and 3 honorable mentions at closing ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Information Mailing Address:  ATTN: Kathy &amp;amp; Jenny Sooy 444 West Third Street Dayton, OH 45402-1460
 DAYMUNC Contact Information </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Country Assignments</title>
      <link>http://daymunc.org/country/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 11:06:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://daymunc.org/country/</guid>
      <description>DAYMUNC Country Assignments We are accepting Country Assignments starting November 13th to November 19th (early preference submission). Country Assignments can absolutely change after the early preference submission deadline.
Country Assignment Rules:  If you are attending NMUN, and we have your team’s country assignment, your delegation will have special preference for that country. Meaning your delegates are guaranteed that country for committees. (For example, if your delegation is representing the United Kingdom at NMUN.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>